<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on LampStand</title>
    <link>https://shina-m.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on LampStand</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.madamori.org/&#34;&gt;madamori.org&lt;/a&gt; 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 07:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shina-m.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jesus Christ, Our Example</title>
      <link>https://shina-m.github.io/posts/jesus-christ-our-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shina-m.github.io/posts/jesus-christ-our-example/</guid>
      <description>I was recently reading Matt 26:30 where it says that Jesus sang a hymn. This is the only time in Jesus&#39; life where it says He sang a hymn. As someone who isn&amp;rsquo;t great at singing, I was curious about how good a singer Jesus would have been. However, this led me to ask a bigger question: &amp;ldquo;How talented/skilled was Jesus in the day-to-day activities he had to engage in on it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Million Dollar Checks</title>
      <link>https://shina-m.github.io/2022/01/million-dollar-checks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 05:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shina-m.github.io/2022/01/million-dollar-checks.html</guid>
      <description>This morning I was reminded of someone who caused me a lot of harm a few years ago, and I was tempted to think unkindly of that person. However, The Lord reminded me of the instruction to love even my enemies. He also reminded me of all the good He has produced out of that same. This reminder produced genuine love in my heart. I also pictured an enemy writing a million dollar check in my name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How we met</title>
      <link>https://shina-m.github.io/2021/12/wedding-testimony-part-1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 21:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shina-m.github.io/2021/12/wedding-testimony-part-1.html</guid>
      <description>His Story In my teenage years, I was a very shy and timid individual. I found it difficult to talk to new people, especially females. Thus, I had little to no female friends. However, in 2013, I began chatting with a female friend more frequently, and I began fancying the idea of a romantic relationship with her. By this time, I was already born-again, and I knew God wanted me to get married at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>His LovingKindness is Everlasting</title>
      <link>https://shina-m.github.io/2020/06/his-lovingkindness-is-everlasting.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shina-m.github.io/2020/06/his-lovingkindness-is-everlasting.html</guid>
      <description>We lie in shame and in dishonor, for we and our fathers have sinned from childhood against the Lord our God; we have not obeyed him. O Israel, if you will truly return to me and absolutely discard your idols, and if you will swear by me alone, the living God, and begin to live good, honest, clean lives, then you will be a testimony to the nations of the world, and they will come to me and glorify my name.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
